泰塔斯维尔是布里瓦德县的县城所在地，与卡纳维拉尔角相邻，而卡角就处在布里瓦德县内
Welcome to Titusville Florida.
欢迎来到佛罗里达州的泰塔斯维尔市
One of the smaller cities along the Space Coast and the place I call home.
这里是太空海岸的一个小城市 也是我的家
原作者名：NASASpaceflight
视频来源：youtu.be/RM7XOEyW-B4
原视频发布日期：20200605
字幕翻译/压制：旋火
I'm Julia Bergeron, NSF's local booster chaser and occasional launch photographer.
我是Julia Bergeron，NSF的本地(猎鹰9号)助推器的追踪员和偶尔的发射摄影师
We're going to take a moment of our stream
我们将利用直播的时间
so I can tell you a little bit about what the space program means to our community.
来告诉你一点关于太空计划对我们社区意味着什么
And what it has been like since the Shuttle program.
以及自从航天飞机计划以来发生了什么
The year was 2011. Atlantis wheels stopped.
那年是2011年 亚特兰蒂斯不再前进
Constellation cancelled.
星座计划被砍
No Buck Rogers in sight.
新的航天计划还没影子
But there was Dave still selling hot dogs at a very empty Miracle City Mall.
但是Dave还在卖热狗 在非常空旷的奇迹城购物中心
Just like he had for the past 41 years.
就像他过去41年一样
Titusville has had ups and downs and many have to do with the space program.
泰特斯维尔有起有落 很多都与太空计划有关
After men walked on the moon and Apollo was no more, the economy took a hit.
在人类走上月球 阿波罗计划结束之后 经济受到了冲击
And it just kept coming with each new program and cancellation.
而且随着每一个新计划的出现和取消 它就不断地出现
Before Apollo the economy was blue crabs mullet in origins.
在阿波罗之前 经济依赖于渔业
After Apollo every third house was empty.
阿波罗之后 三分之一的房子都是空的
Locals wished it had stayed the way it was before the Rockets took over Cape.
当地人都希望它能保持在火箭进入卡角之前的样子
Even today, there can be bitter feelings from those who had to relocate their homestead
即使在今天 那些不得不搬迁家园的人也会感到苦恼
when Cape Kennedy needed land and privacy.
当肯尼迪角需要土地和保密时
The city slogan is launched from here.
城市的标语就是从这里开始的
We see the launch pads with the sunrise a mere 12 miles across the Indian River Lagoon.
在印第安河泻湖对面仅12英里的地方就能看到发射台和日出
There is an almost reluctant embrace with space.
这是一种对太空很勉强的接受
We have streets named for missiles, astronauts and orbiters.
我们有以导弹 宇航员和(航天飞机)轨道器命名的街道
But we didn't truly develop the area for tourism like Cocoa Beach.
但我们并没有像可可比奇那样真正开发当地的旅游业
Although we are getting a beach wear shop on the way to Playa Linda
虽然我们在去琳达海滩的路上有了一家海滩服装店
so it's starting to happen.
那么可以说这开始发展了
We live in a small feeling town with some really big rockets that light up the coast.
我们生活在一个大火箭照亮了海岸的小城市
I moved here in 2016
我是2016年搬到这里的
That's when ULA was doing government and science missions with Atlas and Delta and their families.
那时候 联合发射联盟正在通过宇宙神和德尔塔火箭家族完成政府和科学的任务
And SpaceX was finding their way and had just begun to recover boosters.
而SpaceX公司也找到了自己的方向 并刚刚开始回收助推器
Some pretty exciting things were happening and people started being interested again.
一些相当令人兴奋的事情发生了 而人们开始再次对此产生了兴趣
The Falcon heavy launch brought crowds that Titusville was not prepared for.
泰特斯维尔没准备好重型猎鹰火箭的发射给带来了大量的人群
We knew what would be big.
我们知道会有什么大事发生
But not three hours to get home from the visitors center big.
但不会达到从游客中心回家要花三个小时那么影响大的事情
So how did Titusville forget.
那么泰特斯维尔怎么会忘记
135 Shuttle missions had launched from here right.
135次航天飞机任务都是从这里发射的对吧
It wasn't that long ago. I mean really.
我真觉得这不是很久以前的事了
Although it really does feel like it is.
虽然感觉像是它过去了很久
Well, after Atlantis landed about eight thousand pink slips were handed out.
好吧 亚特兰蒂斯号着陆后 大概解雇了8000多人
Mostly to the employees of the contractors
大部分是给承包商的雇员
that cared for the orbiters and all that came with them.
主要是负责航天飞机轨道器相关工作的人员
No astronauts from here meant no crew quarters staff.
宇航员不来这儿 意味着不需要人来负责乘员宿舍的工作
No cooks and no orbiters to care for.
不需要厨师 也不需要维护航天飞机轨道器
Many had made it their career.
许多人已经把它作为他们的事业
Some are close to retirement.
有些人已经接近退休
The jobs that remained in the area were not close to the salary they needed.
留在这里的工作与他们所需的薪水并不相近
Nor did they require the skills they had to offer.
也不需要他们所能提供的技能
We mostly forgot because many had to leave the area.
我们大多忘记了 因为许多人不得不离开这个地区
Unemployment was at 12%.
失业率达到了12%
Foreclosure was imminent again.
资产拍卖又要即将发生
But slowly we are coming to a new normal.
但我们正慢慢地来到一个新常态
Well at least before COVID made this launch in particular a challenge.
好吧 至少在COVID爆发之前是这样 而COVID使这次发射变成了挑战
Unemployment numbers were below 4%.
失业率低于4%
Vacant properties have been torn down.
空置的房产已经被拆掉了
Miracle City Mall is now Titus landing.
奇迹城购物中心现在是泰特斯维尔游客的最常去的地方
The old Howard Johnson's is about to be condos.
旧的豪生酒店即将成为公寓
The hotels right off the NASA causeway are new for the area
NASA堤道旁的酒店是当地的新建筑
and actually directed toward tourism and promoting our space industry.
实际上是直接面向旅游业的建设 并促进航天产业的发展
And now the Commercial Crew Program has really come to life
而现在 商业载人计划已经开始实施了
5月23日的湿彩排
with the launch of Bob and Doug hopefully today to the International Space Station.
鲍勃和道格有望在今天发射到国际空间站
Finally is something I have heard from many of our business owners around here.
最后是我从这里许多企业主那里听到的消息
Each milestone mission of Dragon, Starliner and Orion has brought bigger crowds back to the area.
龙飞船 星际客机和猎户座的每个里程碑任务都给当地带来了更多的人群
The best I have to offer you at home or watching from the spot you have carved out
不管你在家还是准备好在特别的地方看发射
is that we are all so excited for this launch even though this one's a challenge.
我们都对这次发射感到兴奋 尽管这次是个挑战
Everybody here we're ready for a party.
在座的各位我们已经准备好了一个聚会
We hope you visit again
我们希望你能再次光临
when we can really share our history and the excitement of watching crew launch from home.
当我们可以真正分享我们的历史以及在家观看载人发射的兴奋
There are passionate volunteers at local museums who would love to bend your ear.
当地博物馆里有热情的志愿者 他们很愿意为你讲解
Friendly shopkeepers and restaurant tours who would be happy to see you again.
友好的店主会很高兴再见到你
I hope the next time crew launches from home,
希望下次家门口的载人发射
our new normal will be back to something more familiar.
我们的新常态将变回更加熟悉的东西
They say love where you live.
他们说 爱你住的地方
I say there isn't anywhere else I would rather be.
我说 我只会住在这儿了
祝鲍勃和道格好运